(Penny:)No, you made that for you.
I want you to have it.
(Bernadette:)We know you're upset,
and you have every right to be...
...but we'd like a second chance
to make things right.
(Penny:)We are really sorry.
(Penny:)We were trying to think of some way to
show you how much we care about you.
(Bernadette:)Which is why
it would mean so much...
(Bernadette:)...if you would agree
to be the maid of honor at my wedding.
(Sheldon:)What?
(Amy:)Wait, is this some kind
of practical joke?
Like in Norway when my "friends"
trapped me in a sauna with a horny otter?
(Bernadette:)No. I... I want you
to be the maid of honor.
(Amy:)Oh, my gosh.
No one's ever asked me
to be the maid of honor.
(Amy:)Well, that's not true.
Once, but then they all died.
- So is that a yes?
- Yes, heh. Yes.
(Amy:)Oh, my gosh, I...
I have so much to do.
(Amy:)There's the bridal shower
and the bachelorette party.
What should we do for the bachelorette?
Oh, I know.
(Amy:)Go to a Native American sweat lodge,
take peyote, roll in mud...